http://www.live365.com/legal/privacy

Start Your StationSelect...1. IntroductionThanks for choosing Live365!At Live365, we want to give you the best possible experience to ensure that you enjoy our service today, tomorrow, and in the future. Your privacy and the security of your personal data is, and will always be, enormously important to us. So, we want to transparently explain how and why we gather, store, share and use your personal data - as well as outline and choices you have around when and how you choose to share your personal data.That is our objective, and this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) will explain exactly what we mean in further detail below.2. About this PolicyThis Policy sets out the essential details relating to your personal data relationship with Live365. The Policy applies to all Live365 services and any associated services (referred to as the ‘Live365 Service’). The terms governing your use of the Live365 Service are defined in our Terms of Service.From time to time, we may develop new or offer additional services. If the introduction of these new or additional services results in any change to the way we collect or process your personal data we will provide you with more information and additional terms or policies. Unless stated otherwise when we introduce these new or additional services, they will be subject to this Policy.The aim of this Policy is to:Ensure that you understand what personal data we collect about you, the reasons why we collect and use it, and who we share it with;Explain the way we use the personal data that you share with us in order to give you a great experience when you are using the Live365 Service; andExplain your rights and choices in relation to the personal data we collect and process about you and how we will protect your privacy.We hope this helps you to understand our privacy commitments to you. For information on how to contact us if you ever have any questions or concerns, please see the ‘How to Contact Us’ section below. Alternatively, if you do not agree with the content of this Policy, then please remember it is your choice whether you want to use the Live365 Service.3. Your rights and your preferences: Giving you choice and controlYou may be aware that a new European Union law, called the General Data Protection Regulation or "GDPR" gives certain rights to individuals in relation to their personal data. Accordingly, we have implemented additional transparency and have the ability to allow you to remove data you submitted from the Live365 Service at your own wish. As available and except as limited under applicable law, the rights afforded to individuals are:Right of Access - the right to be informed of and request access to the personal data we process about you;Right to Rectification - the right to request that we amend or update your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete;Right to Erasure - the right to request that we delete your personal data;Right to Restrict - the right to request that we temporarily or permanently stop processing all or some of your personal data;Right to Object - the right, at any time, to object to us processing your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation;the right to object to your personal data being processed for direct marketing purposes;Right to Data Portability - the right to request a copy of your personal data in electronic format and the right to transmit that personal data for use in another party’s service;If you have any questions about your privacy, your rights, or how to exercise them, please contact us at privacy@live365.com. We will respond to your request within a reasonable period of time upon verification of your identity.4. How do we collect your personal data?We collect your personal data in the following ways:When you sign up for the Live365 Service - when you sign up to the Live365 Service, we collect certain personal data so you can use the Live365 Service such as your email address, name, address, and phone.From third parties - we will receive personal data about you and your activity from third parties, including advertisers and partners we work with in order to provide you with the Live365 Service (please see ‘Sharing your personal data’ section
below). We will use this personal data either where you have provided your consent to the third party or to Live365 to that data sharing taking place or where Live365 has a legitimate interest to use the personal data in order to provide you with the Live365 Service.We use anonymized and aggregated information for purposes that include testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, creating marketing and promotion models, improving the Live365 Service, and developing new features and functionality within the Live365 Service.5. What personal data do we collect from you?We have set out in the tables below the categories of personal data we collect and use about you:Categories of personal dataDescription of categoryAccount Registration DataIf you register with Live365, you must provide us with your first + last name, a valid email address, and a password to create your account. You may additionally provide your mailing address and phone number. When creating a station, you must provide us with the station name, website url, logo (optionally), station profile cover art (optionally), genres, description (optional), and links to your social media account (optional).SubscriptionWhen signing up for a paid package, you will be required to submit your credit card number so our third party service provider can process payments related to the Live365 Service.CommunicationWhen communicating with Live365 staff, such as through Live Chat or a Support Ticket, we collect and log the information you submit to us. If subscribing to a Newsletter, we will collect information from you such as your email address.Location InformationWe infer your location by utilizing your IP address to determine a general geographic region. This information is used for advertising targeting and compliance with regulatory laws as it relates to music copyrights.Device InformationWe obtain information such as your IP address, web browser type, mobile operating system, and unique device identifiers. This information is used for counting metrics internally and with logging for errors as it relates to the Live365 Service.Cookies & Related TechnologiesWhen you visit the Live365 Service, we and our third party service providers receive and record information from your browser and from cookies and similar technologies. Learn more about how we use cookies and related technologies in our Cookie Policy.6. What do we use your personal data for?Categories of usageDescription of categoryInternal and Service-Related UsageWe use personal data for internal and Service-related purposes, including to operate, provide, and maintain the Live365 Service.Analytics & Bug ReportsWe use the data we collect such as your location to monitor the performance and health of the Live365 Service and continually improve the experience.CommunicationWe may send emails to you for billing, customer or technical support purposes, newsletters, or other topics we may find relevant for you based on your subscription to the Live365 Service.AdvertisingWe and our advertising partners may use your personal data, including location, to deliver advertisements targeted to you.Aggregate DataWe may de-identify and aggregate information collected through the use of the Live365 Service for statistical analysis and other lawful purposes.7. Sharing your personal dataWe have set out the categories of recipients of the personal data collected or generated through your use of the Live365 Service.Publicly available informationInformation including your station name, website URL, station logo, station profile cover art, social media account links, genres, and station description (‘Public Information’) will be available publicly and to be utilized by other Live365 users.Non Affiliated CompaniesWe do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes.Social Networking & Other WebsitesLive365 may allow you or other users to Public Information you submit to the Live365 Service with social networking and other sites, such as your station’s name with now playing information. We do not share your personal data with other websites unless you direct the Live365 Service to do so.Search EnginesYour Public Information submitted to the Live365 Service will be available to search engines, such as Google or Bing, just like any normal social media service.Other Third PartiesLive365 may disclose your personal data to third parties in the following circumstances:With Your Consent We may disclose personal data. We may seek permission from you in different ways, such as an Opt In when signing up for the Live365 Service.To Comply with Legal Obligations We may access, preserve, and disclose personal data or other account information if we believe it is required to comply with laws or other legal obligations that may ariseIn case of a Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfer If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, or liquidation, Live365 may be sold or transferred as part of a transaction to ensure continued success of the Live365 Service. The continued use of your personal data shall be governed by Live365’ Privacy Policy in effect at the time of the transaction.8. Data retention and deletionWe keep your personal data only as long as necessary to provide you with the Live365 Service and for legitimate and essential business purposes, such as maintaining the performance of the Live365 Service, making data-driven business decisions about new features and offerings, complying with our legal obligations, and resolving disputes.We keep some of your personal data for as long as you are a user of the Live365 Service. For example, we keep your playlists, station information, media library, and account information.If you request, we will delete or anonymize your personal data so that it no longer identifies you, unless we are legally allowed or required to maintain certain personal data, including situations such as the following:If there is an unresolved issue relating to your account, such as an outstanding credit on your account or an unresolved claim or dispute we will retain the necessary personal data until the issue is resolved;Where we are required to retain the personal data for our legal, tax, audit, and accounting obligations, we will retain the necessary personal data for the period required by applicable law; and/or,Where necessary for our legitimate business interests such as fraud prevention or to maintain the security of our users.9. LinksWe may display advertisements from third parties and other content that links to third-party websites. We cannot control or be held responsible for third parties’ privacy practices and content. If you click on a third-party advertisement or link, please understand that you are leaving the Live365 Service and any personal data you provide will not be covered by this Policy. Please read their privacy policies to find out how they collect and process your personal data.10. Keeping your personal data safeWe are committed to protecting our users’ personal data. We implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to help protect the security of your personal data; however, please note that no system is ever completely secure. We have implemented various policies including pseudonymization, encryption, access, and retention policies to guard against unauthorized access and unnecessary retention of personal data in our systems.Your password protects your user account, so we encourage you to use a unique and strong password, limit access to your computer and browser, and log out after having used the Live365 Service.11. ChildrenThe Live365 Service is not directed to children under the age of 13 years. However, in some countries, stricter age limits may apply under local law. Please see our Terms of Service for further details.We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13 years or under the applicable age limit (the “Age Limit”). If you are under the Age Limit, please do not use the Live365 Service, and do not provide any personal data to us.If you are a parent of a child under the Age Limit and become aware that your child has provided personal data to Live365, please contact us at privacy@live365.com, and you may request exercise of your applicable rights detailed in the ‘Your rights and your preferences: Giving you choice and control’ Section 3 of this Policy.If we learn that we have collected the personal data of a child under the age of 13 years, we will take reasonable steps to delete the personal data. This may require us to delete the Live365 account for that child.12. Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may occasionally make changes to this Policy.When we make material changes to this Policy, we’ll provide you with prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances, e.g., by displaying a prominent notice within the Live365 Service or by sending you an email. We may notify you in advance.Please, therefore, make sure you read any such notice carefully.How to Contact UsThank you for reading our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us.Live3651340 Monticello AvenueHermitage, PA 16148privacy@live365.comLive365 is the data controller for the purposes of the personal data processed under this Policy.Podcast HostingChristmas MusicWhere to ListenBroadcaster ResourcesAbout UsBlogCareersSupport© 2020 Live365TermsDMCAPrivacyCookies
